http://www.asset-intertech.com/company/privacy-information

Privacy Information | ASSET InterTech
Register | LoginGoogle search
Toggle navigation
Press ReleaseProductseResourcesCompanySupportBlog
CompanyAwardsContactManagementEmploymentPoliciesPress Press ReleasesCase StudiesMedia Resources
Privacy Information
ASSET InterTech, Inc. Online Privacy NoticeASSET InterTech, Inc. (ASSET) respects your privacy. We also want to provide you with the best possible experience when working with our products, support and services. In so doing, ASSET may collect individual identifying information (Information) about you, your computer or the licenses you are using. This Online Privacy Notice is made available to you to make you aware of how ASSET collects and uses Information ASSET may collect through use of ASSET products, website, web tools, or sales and support engagements.This Privacy Notice may change without any additional notice, so you are encouraged to review this policy regularly or anytime you have a concern about your privacy. Your continued use of any of our products, website, web tools means that you accept the changes to this Privacy Statement.1.  IntroductionThis privacy notice provides you with details of how we collect and process your personal data through your use of our site www.asset-intertech.com.By providing us with your data, you warrant to us that you are over 13 years of age.ASSET InterTech is the data controller and we are responsible for your personal data (referred to as “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy notice).It is very important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. Please let us know if at any time your personal information changes by emailing us at gdpr@asset-intertech.com2.  What Data Do We Collect About You, For What Purpose and On What Ground We Process It.Personal data means any information capable of identifying an individual. It does not include anonymized data.We may process the following categories of personal data about you:Communication Data that includes any communication that you send to us whether that be through the contact form on our website, through email, text, social media messaging, social media posting or any other communication that you send us. We process this data for the purposes of communicating with you, for record keeping and for the establishment, pursuance or defense of legal claims. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to reply to communications sent to us, to keep records and to establish, pursue or defend legal claims.Customer Data that includes data relating to any purchases of goods and/or services such as your name, title, billing address, delivery address, email address, phone number, contact details, purchase details and your card details. We process this data to supply the goods and/or services you have purchased and to keep records of such transactions. Our lawful ground for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps at your request to enter into such a contract.User Data that includes data about how you use our website and any online services together with any data that you post for publication on our website or through other online services. We process this data to operate our website and ensure relevant content is provided to you, to ensure the security of our website, to maintain back- ups of our website and/or databases and to enable publication and administration of our website, other online services and business. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to enable us to properly administer our website and our business.Technical Data from website that includes data about your use of our website and online services such as your IP address, your login data, details about your browser, length of visit to pages on our website, page views and navigation paths, details about the number of times you use our website, time zone settings and other technology on the devices you use to access our website. The source of this data is from our analytics tracking system. We process this data to analyze your use of our website and other online services, to administer and protect our business and website, to deliver relevant content and advertisements to you and to understand the effectiveness of our advertising.  Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to enable us to properly administer our website and our business and to grow our business and to decide our marketing strategy.Technical Data from product usage that includes information about your application of ASSET products, computer host identifiers, computer operating systems, version numbers of installed ASSET products and other technology on the devices you use to access our products. The source of this data is from purchase of our products, support of our products, or services. We process this data to:improve products and servicescreate license filesrespond to your requests for supportprovide customized support for your application of ASSET productspersonalize your experience on our website and web-based toolssend product updates or evaluate need and eligibility for product updatessend announcements or marketing informationprocess your ordervalidate or enable legal use of licensesperform research and data analysisperform auditsupdate sales and support databasesFor the purpose of providing quality products and timely support and services, ASSET may make Information available to trusted third parties, including business partners, distributors, consultants, auditors, and contracted service providers.Marketing Data that includes data about your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences. We process this data to enable you to partake in our promotions such as competitions, prize draws and free giveaways, to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of this advertising.  Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to decide our marketing strategy.We may use Customer Data, User Data, Technical Data and Marketing Data to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you (including Facebook adverts or other display advertisements) and to measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve you. Our lawful ground for this processing is legitimate interests which is to grow our business. We may also use such data to send other marketing communications to you. Our lawful ground for this processing is either consent or legitimate interests (namely to grow our business).3.  How We Collect Your Personal DataWe may collect data about you by you providing the data directly to us (for example by filling in forms on our site or by sending us emails). We may automatically collect certain data from you as you use our website by using cookies and similar technologies or collect information through:use of the ASSET website and its community functionsuse of active server pages called while using ASSET productssales, support and service engagements via phone or emaildirect entry into our on-line database for customer supporton-line surveysftp transfersPlease see our cookie policy for more details about this.We may receive data from third parties such as analytics providers such as Google based outside the EU, advertising networks such as Facebook based outside the EU, such as search information providers such as Google based outside the EU, providers of technical, payment and delivery services, such as data brokers or aggregators.We may also receive data from publicly availably sources such as Companies House and the Electoral Register based inside the EU.4.  Marketing CommunicationsOur lawful ground of processing your personal data to send you marketing communications is either your consent or our legitimate interests (namely to grow our business).Under the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations, we may send you marketing communications from us if (i) you made a purchase or asked for information from us about our goods or services or (ii) you agreed to receive marketing communications and, in each case, you have not opted out of receiving such communications since. Under these regulations, if you are a limited company, we may send you marketing emails without your consent. However you can still opt out of receiving marketing emails from us at any time.Before we share your personal data with any third party for their own marketing purposes we will get your express consent.You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by logging into the website and checking or unchecking relevant boxes to adjust your marketing preferences or by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or by emailing us at gdpr@asset-intertech.com at any time.If you opt out of receiving marketing communications this opt-out does not apply to personal data provided as a result of other transactions, such as purchases, warranty registrations etc.5.  Disclosures of Your Personal DataWe may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below:Other companies in our group who provide services to us.Service providers who provide IT and system administration services.Professional advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurersGovernment bodies that require us to report processing activities.Third parties to whom we sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets.We require all third parties to whom we transfer your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We only allow such third parties to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.6.  International TransfersAs a general rule, we do not transfer your personal data outside the European Economic Area (EEA). However, in limited and necessary circumstances, your personal data may be transferred outside of the EEA for legitimate business purposes.Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we will do our best to ensure a similar degree of security of data by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is in place:We will only transfer your personal data to countries that the European Commission have approved as providing an adequate level of protection for personal data by; orWhere we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts or codes of conduct or certification mechanisms approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe; orIf we use US-based providers that are part of EU-US Privacy Shield, we may transfer data to them, as they have equivalent safeguards in place.If none of the above safeguards is available, we may request your explicit consent to the specific transfer. You will have the right to withdraw this consent at any time.7.  Data SecurityWe have put in place security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used, altered, disclosed, or accessed without authorization. We also allow access to your personal data only to those employees and partners who have a business need to know such data. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they must keep it confidential. If you supply credit card information to ASSET on-line purchasing processes, use a browser enabled for Secure Sockets Layer, and the information will be protected during transmission over the Internet and will be used only for processing the order. Visibility of Information you supply in the website community is subject to the preferences you set in your profile; you are responsible for maintaining the profile and protecting the Information you type in that forum. Information you upload to a private ftp folder set up by ASSET will be visible only to you and to ASSET employees. If you identify Information you supply to ASSET as ITAR-restricted, the information will be made visible only to ASSET employees who are U.S. citizens.We have procedures in place to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach if we are legally required to.8.  Data RetentionWe will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.When deciding what the correct time is to keep the data for we look at its amount, nature and sensitivity, potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure, the processing purposes, if these can be achieved by other means and legal requirements.For tax purposes the law requires us to keep basic information about our customers (including Contact, Identity, Financial and Transaction Data) for six years after they stop being customers.In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal data for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.9.  Your Legal RightsUnder data protection laws you have rights in relation to your personal data that include the right to request access, correction, erasure, restriction, transfer, to object to processing, to portability of data and (where the lawful ground of processing is consent) to withdraw consent.You can see more about these rights at:https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protectio...If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please email us at gdpr@asset-intertech.com.You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive or refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you.If you are not happy with any aspect of how we collect and use your data, you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We should be grateful if you would contact us first if you do have a complaint so that we can try to resolve it for you.10.  Third-Party LinksThis website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.11.  CookiesYou can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. For more information about the cookies we use, please see Cookie Policy.
Points of InterestSoftware DebugChip DebugHardware ValidationManufacturing TesteResourcesSoftware Debug eBooksChip Debug eBooksHardware Validation eBooksManufacturing Test eBooksVideosProductsSourcePoint for IntelSourcePoint for ARMBoundary-Scan TestProcessor-Controlled TestIJTAG TestEmbedded DiagnosticsFPGA-Controlled TestHardware for SourcePointHardware for ScanWorksCompanyContact / SalesEventsManagementPress ReleasesCase StudiesMedia ResourcesSupportTrainingServicesSupport PoliciesASSET Corporate Contact
ASSET InterTech 2201 N. Central Expy., Ste 105 Richardson, TX 75080 P: (888) 694-6250Social Network@ASSETInterTechASSET on LinkedInASSET on FacebookASSET BlogCopyright ©2020 ASSET InterTech. All rights reserved. | Privacy Notice | Cookie Policy
